<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on PowerShell DevOps and Cloud Conference 2021</title>
    <link>https://pdcconf.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on PowerShell DevOps and Cloud Conference 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://pdcconf.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/speakers/aditi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/speakers/aditi/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science student passionate about venturing into newer, niche fields in the subject and giving them her all! I am interested in exploring possibilities in fields off the beaten track and collaborating with and learning from like-minded peers on the same. Open to challenges and opportunities, technical or otherwise! Strong professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Computer Science from PES University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/speakers/anamika/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/speakers/anamika/</guid>
      <description>An Open-Source enthusiast &amp;amp; a junior pursuing my Bachelors in Computer Science &amp;amp; Engineering. I have a fair knowledge in Python Programming Language. Looking for great opportunities where I can contribute towards upcoming technology innovations and manage key projects that impact the organization, as well as broaden my scope of learning from the organization&amp;rsquo;s team members, hence enhancing my skills and experience. Some key possessions include good communication skills, written and verbal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/speakers/arun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/speakers/arun/</guid>
      <description>Arun P V is a Professional Certified Coach (ICF credentialed) with 700+ hours of coaching experience. Arun has over two decades of corporate experience in the IT Industry with 18+ years in various mentoring &amp;amp; leadership roles in multinational organisations like NIIT, Microland and Dimension Data. He has coached several business leaders and hundreds of managers across India. As a Life Coach, he has enabled individuals to move ahead in the pursuit of their life and career goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/speakers/gowri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/speakers/gowri/</guid>
      <description>Indian Shades Art Management is creating a thriving atmosphere for the Arts in many spheres of the contemporary world.
We engage with organisations to deliver L&amp;amp;D programs and Employee engagements in a never-before-seen format. Give us 45 minutes; gain a team which is refreshed, happy and raring to go. With an array of virtualin-person and hybrid programs, we are an organisation&amp;rsquo;s best friend when it comes to adding a little bit of zing to everyday activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/speakers/satyavel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/speakers/satyavel/</guid>
      <description>Head of product for Azure Infrastructure as Code offering (Azure Resource Manager, Bicep) and Governance offering (Azure Blueprints). The Azure deployment and governance services portfolio focuses on enabling enterprise to quickly and easily create and manage Azure resources at scale while providing the necessary guard rails for Enterprises to ensure data security, compliance and enforcing organization standards.
Responsible for defining product strategy and core deployment platform services and tools in Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/speakers/vikas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/speakers/vikas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ajay Kakkar</title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/ajay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/ajay/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alok Agarwal</title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/alok/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/alok/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chendrayan Venkatesan</title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/chen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>1. Purpose A primary goal of GDG Toulouse is to be inclusive to the largest number of contributors, with the most varied and diverse backgrounds possible. As such, we are committed to providing a friendly, safe and welcoming environment for all, regardless of gender, sexual orientation, ability, ethnicity, socioeconomic status, and religion (or lack thereof). GDG Toulouse prides itself on being an open, respectful, and inclusive community. That means the jerky behavior isn’t allowed at GDG meetings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deepak Dhami</title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/deepak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/deepak/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jaap Brasser</title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/jaap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/jaap/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prasoon Karunan V</title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/prasoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/prasoon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prateek Singh</title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/prateek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/prateek/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravikanth Chaganti</title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/ravikanth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/ravikanth/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunish Surendran</title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/sunish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/team/core/sunish/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
