<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sponsors on PowerShell DevOps and Cloud Conference 2021</title>
    <link>https://pdcconf.in/partners/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sponsors on PowerShell DevOps and Cloud Conference 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://pdcconf.in/partners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CloudLabsAI</title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/partners/gold/spektrasystems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/partners/gold/spektrasystems/</guid>
      <description>CloudLabs, provides easy-to-use, high-performance hands-on lab experience to companies of all sizes. We cater to the IT companies, educational organizations, training partners and more. It is for those that wish to exhibit innovative business ideas, enable effective technical upskilling, and present optimized solutions for training transformation. With CloudLabs, organizations can deliver fast and reliable cloud infrastructures that exceed business objectives effortlessly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/partners/support/microsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/partners/support/microsoft/</guid>
      <description>We are glad and ecnouraged to have support from Microsoft </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tecoholic</title>
      <link>https://pdcconf.in/partners/support/tecoholic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pdcconf.in/partners/support/tecoholic/</guid>
      <description>Tecoholic – The Global Tech Community Platform is an open community platform, which has been build “by community for community”. We connect industry professionals, vertical experts, and learners together bringing real-world relevance and career exposure for enhanced learning.
We are continuously growing our community to help organizations in capability building with Skills-based learning. In the ever changing job roles, extending the learning outreach by nurturing the future ready and most desired professionals in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
